<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on DavHau - David Hauer</title>
    <link>https://DavHau.com/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on DavHau - David Hauer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://DavHau.com/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>dream2nix</title>
      <link>https://DavHau.com/projects/dream2nix/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://DavHau.com/projects/dream2nix/</guid>
      <description>!!! Warning: dream2nix is unstable software. While simple UX is one of our main focus points, the APIs are still under development. Do expect changes that will break your setup.
Ecosystem stats: Link to heading Funding Link to heading This project was funded through the NGI Assure Fund, a fund established by NLnet with financial support from the European Commission&amp;rsquo;s Next Generation Internet programme, under the aegis of DG Communications Networks, Content and Technology under grant agreement No 957073.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>drv-parts</title>
      <link>https://DavHau.com/projects/drv-parts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://DavHau.com/projects/drv-parts/</guid>
      <description>drv-parts Link to heading This is experimental, use with care!
drv-parts replaces callPackage, override, overrideAttrs, ... as a mechanism for configuring packages. It makes package configuration feel similar to NixOS system configuration.
This is an implementation of ideas first drafted at DavHau/pkgs-modules.
It is recommended to use drv-parts through flake-parts (see examples/flake-parts).
There is also support for flake-less usage (see examples/no-flake).
Funding by NLNet Link to heading drv-parts was funded as part of the dream2nix project through the NGI Assure Fund, a fund established by NLnet with financial support from the European Commission&amp;rsquo;s Next Generation Internet programme, under the aegis of DG Communications Networks, Content and Technology under grant agreement No 957073.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mach-nix</title>
      <link>https://DavHau.com/projects/mach-nix/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://DavHau.com/projects/mach-nix/</guid>
      <description>!!! This project is unmaintained. The plan is to replace it with dream2nix. The dream2nix python support is still WIP and needs your help. Please consider to support dream2nix with contributions or funds in order to speed up the process. Feel free to contact me.
mach-nix - Create highly reproducible python environments Link to heading Mach-nix makes it easy to create and share reproducible python environments or packages. Existing tools for python package management often suffer from reproducibility and complexity issues, requiring a multitude of tools and additional virtualization layers to work sufficiently.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>nix-portable</title>
      <link>https://DavHau.com/projects/nix-portable/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://DavHau.com/projects/nix-portable/</guid>
      <description>Nix as a static executable requiring no configuration, privileges, or (user) namespaces.
For binary downloads check the releases page.
Goals: Link to heading make it extremely simple to install nix make nix work in restricted environments (containers, HPC, &amp;hellip;) be able to use the official binary cache (by simulating the /nix/store) make it easy to distribute nix (via other package managers) Tested on the following systems/environments: Link to heading Distros (x86_64): Arch Linux CentOS 7 Debian Fedora NixOS Ubuntu Distros (aarch64): Debian Other Environments: Docker (debian image) Github Actions Under the hood: Link to heading The nix-portable executable is a self extracting archive, caching its contents in $HOME/.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>systemd2nix</title>
      <link>https://DavHau.com/projects/systemd2nix/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://DavHau.com/projects/systemd2nix/</guid>
      <description> systemd2nix Link to heading Convert systemd service files to nix syntax for nixpkgs
Install Link to heading nix-env -if https://github.com/DavHau/systemd2nix/tarball/master Usage Link to heading systemd2nix &amp;lt; example.service </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
